<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kumar Aniket on Random</title>
    <link>/authors/aniket/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kumar Aniket on Random</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2022 &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.aniket.co.uk/&#34;&gt;Kumar Aniket&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 21:41:04 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/authors/aniket/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lecture George Freeman</title>
      <link>/posts/2022_04_29_lecture-george-freeman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 21:41:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022_04_29_lecture-george-freeman/</guid>
      <description>Lecture by George Freeman | Meeting Neville Ash
28 April 2022, 17:30
Lecture by George Freeman at Cambridge, organised by CSaP. He talked about the Government&amp;rsquo;s Integrated Science Review. His ambition is to make UK the Science Superpower. He had ambition of increasing the Science spending to European levels.
I asked him the following question. Given the lag between the spending and returns from growth in terms of taxes, isn&amp;rsquo;t it going to clash with the levelling up agenda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Munger on Theory of the Firm</title>
      <link>/posts/2022_04_27_munger_firm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 13:05:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022_04_27_munger_firm/</guid>
      <description>Michael Munger | Firms, Markets and transaction costs
 Michael Munger, Bosses Don’t Wear Bunny Slippers: If Markets are so Great, Why are there Firms?
Michael Munger is Chair of Political Science at Duke University.
Prices are the central force directing resources and shaping consumption in a market economy. But most economic activity seems (at first glance) to take place without any influence from prices at all.
 Most people work for a firm, a company, a large organization, and they have a boss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UCLA School of Economics</title>
      <link>/posts/2022_04_26_ucla_economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 18:28:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022_04_26_ucla_economics/</guid>
      <description>Topics: Universal Economics Book, Property rights, transaction,
 Podcast information David Henderson on the Essential UCLA School of Economics | Conversation Topicss
 Property Rights  The conversation begins with a discussion of Harold Demsetz&amp;rsquo;s 1967 AER article on property rights . Roberts and Henderson agree that this piece would both never be published in a top journal today, and that it remains a path-breaking contribution. What was so significant about this article? How do you think Demsetz’s notion of mutually beneficial exchange compares to the notion of euvoluntary exchange as put forth by Mike Munger?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Books on Markets</title>
      <link>/posts/2022_04_24_market_books_version2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 14:12:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022_04_24_market_books_version2/</guid>
      <description>Interesting books on markets from FT
FT Opinion on Time Warner Inc | Observer US | 11 October 2005
 &amp;ldquo;In life and in business, there are two cardinal sins,” Icahn wrote. “The first is to act precipitously without thought, and the second is to not act at all.&amp;rdquo; by Carl Icahn.
 The World for Sale: Money, Power and the Traders Who Barter the Earth’s Resources (2022)
by Javier Blas and Jack Farchy | Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Links</title>
      <link>/posts/2022_02_18_random_links/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 17:48:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022_02_18_random_links/</guid>
      <description>Random links about this and that.
International standard paper sizes
by Markus Kuhn
Standard paper sizes like ISO A4 are widely used all over the world today. This text explains the ISO 216 paper size system and the ideas behind its design.
The ISO paper size concept
In the ISO paper size system, the height-to-width ratio of all pages is the square root of two (1.4142 : 1). In other words, the width and the height of a page relate to each other like the side and the diagonal of a square.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodreads review on space</title>
      <link>/posts/2022_02_17_goodreads_review_taleb_massey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 16:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022_02_17_goodreads_review_taleb_massey/</guid>
      <description>Review of Space, Place, and Gender by Doreen Massey
Review of Taleb Book by Trevor on Goodreads 
review - interesting philosophy references  Fooled by Randomness: The Hidden Role of Chance in Life and in the Markets | Nassim Nicholas Taleb
Yeah, you see. I’ve just checked and most of the other reviews of this book do pretty much what I thought they would do. They complain about the tone. This guy is never going to win an award for modesty and he probably thinks you are stupid and have wasted your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books on Markets</title>
      <link>/posts/2022_02_17_books_on_markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 16:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022_02_17_books_on_markets/</guid>
      <description>The books on markets
From a goodreads review on Blue Ocean Strategy
The signal-to-noise ratio of business books generally tends towards zero. They fall into one of three categories:
 baked-over platitudes designed to reinforce the self-esteem of the reader (see First Break all the Rules), laughably faulty reasoning (see Good to Great) , and interesting ideas that are overextended and driven into the ground (see The Tipping Point).  There are a few good ideas in the book, but they are shrouded in unnecessary jargon and applied precariously to far too many companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fight back | Timeline</title>
      <link>/posts/2022_02_10_fight_back_timeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 21:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022_02_10_fight_back_timeline/</guid>
      <description>gantt dateFormat YYYY-MM-DD title Adding GANTT diagram functionality to mermaid excludes :excludes the named dates/days from being included in a charted task.. section A section Completed task :done, des1, 2014-01-06,2014-01-08 Active task :active, des2, 2014-01-09, 3d Future task : des3, after des2, 5d Future task2 : des4, after des3, 5d section Critical tasks Completed task in the critical line :crit, done, 2014-01-06,24h Implement parser and jison :crit, done, after des1, 2d Create tests for parser :crit, active, 3d Future task in critical line :crit, 5d Create tests for renderer :2d Add to mermaid :1d        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using python in textmate</title>
      <link>/posts/python_20220208/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/python_20220208/</guid>
      <description>Using python in textmate.
Python in TextMate 2
TextMate will parse the first line of your Python script for a shebang sequence.
... If found, it will attempt to call that interpreter when you run your script. I have installed Python 3 using homebrew, so the binary is in my /usr/local/bin folder. Lets set up a simple script and test this: #!/usr/local/bin/python3 print(&#39;hello, hypepat!&#39;)  .tm_properties
TM_PYTHON = &amp;quot;${CWD}/venv/bin/python&amp;quot; excludeDirectoriesInBrowser = &amp;quot;{__pycache__,include,lib,bin}&amp;quot; includeFilesInBrowser = &amp;quot;{.gitignore}&amp;quot; [ source.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
