<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Economics on Random</title>
    <link>/series/economics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Economics on Random</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2022 &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.aniket.co.uk/&#34;&gt;Kumar Aniket&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 13:05:18 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/series/economics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Munger on Theory of the Firm</title>
      <link>/posts/2022_04_27_munger_firm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 13:05:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022_04_27_munger_firm/</guid>
      <description>Michael Munger | Firms, Markets and transaction costs
 Michael Munger, Bosses Don’t Wear Bunny Slippers: If Markets are so Great, Why are there Firms?
Michael Munger is Chair of Political Science at Duke University.
Prices are the central force directing resources and shaping consumption in a market economy. But most economic activity seems (at first glance) to take place without any influence from prices at all.
 Most people work for a firm, a company, a large organization, and they have a boss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UCLA School of Economics</title>
      <link>/posts/2022_04_26_ucla_economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 18:28:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022_04_26_ucla_economics/</guid>
      <description>Topics: Universal Economics Book, Property rights, transaction,
 Podcast information David Henderson on the Essential UCLA School of Economics | Conversation Topicss
 Property Rights  The conversation begins with a discussion of Harold Demsetz&amp;rsquo;s 1967 AER article on property rights . Roberts and Henderson agree that this piece would both never be published in a top journal today, and that it remains a path-breaking contribution. What was so significant about this article? How do you think Demsetz’s notion of mutually beneficial exchange compares to the notion of euvoluntary exchange as put forth by Mike Munger?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Books on Markets</title>
      <link>/posts/2022_04_24_market_books_version2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 14:12:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022_04_24_market_books_version2/</guid>
      <description>Interesting books on markets from FT
FT Opinion on Time Warner Inc | Observer US | 11 October 2005
 &amp;ldquo;In life and in business, there are two cardinal sins,” Icahn wrote. “The first is to act precipitously without thought, and the second is to not act at all.&amp;rdquo; by Carl Icahn.
 The World for Sale: Money, Power and the Traders Who Barter the Earth’s Resources (2022)
by Javier Blas and Jack Farchy | Link</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
