<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Microfinance on Research</title>
    <link>/literature/microfinance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Microfinance on Research</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2022 &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.aniket.co.uk/&#34;&gt;Kumar Aniket&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 14:41:15 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/literature/microfinance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Savings</title>
      <link>/posts/2022_05_03_savings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 14:41:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2022_05_03_savings/</guid>
      <description>Information and links about savings
A New Paradigm for Microfinance: Savings and Credit | While they are no magic wand and really only work as part of a holistic approach, there is enormous potential for international development organizations to help communities help themselves through savings and credit groups.
Karlan et al 2016 D. Karlan, R. Mann, J. Kendall, R. Pande, T. Suri, and J. Zinman. Making microfinance more effective. Harvard Business Review, pages 2–6, 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mallick Nabin 2018</title>
      <link>/posts/mallick2018cost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mallick2018cost/</guid>
      <description>D. Mallick and M. H. Nabin. Cost effectiveness or serving the poor? Factors determining program placement of NGOs in Bangladesh. Economic modelling, 69:281–290, 2018.
  Notes from Mallick Nabin 2018 consensus on its efficacy as a poverty alleviation tool is still elusive (for a recent survey of the literature, see Banerjee et al. (2015))
microfinance programs in Bangladesh target non-poor households without adhering to screening devices (Amin et al., 2003; Matin, 2005; Morduch, 2011)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sequential Lending ideas</title>
      <link>/posts/sqlideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/sqlideas/</guid>
      <description>Ideas sustainability and expansion depend on loan repayments, as well as on cost effectiveness (sql reduces cost).
NGO coverage is higher in villages with better opportunities for productive activities (Mallick Nabin,2018).
 need mechanisms that allow NGO to alleviate poverty by operating in areas with lower productivity.  From Mallick Nabin 2018 Microfinance organisations target non-poor
 without adhering to screening devices target program locations1 mission drift2  poverty alleviation implies:
 NGO will take the program to the locations where profit-driven financial institutions do not reach and target the poor households in a given location.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
